<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mood Journal</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="action_logout">LOG OUT</string>

    <array name="onboard_titles">
        <item>Hello there</item>
        <item>Reminder</item>
        <item>Phone verification</item>
    </array>

    <array name="onboard_subtitles">
        <item>Tell us a bit more about yourself, so we can help you record your mood every day.
        </item>
        <item>We\'ll send you a daily reminder, so you won\'t forget to record your mood.</item>
        <item></item>
    </array>

    <array name="questions">
        <item>What should we call you?</item>
        <item>what time should we remind you?</item>
        <item>We need to verify your phone, don\'t worry, we will keep your number safe &amp;
            private.
        </item>
    </array>

    <array name="phq_questions">
        <item>Little interest or pleasure in doing things</item>
        <item>Feeling down, depressed, or hopeless</item>
        <item>Trouble falling or staying asleep, or sleeping too much</item>
        <item>Feeling tired or having little energy</item>
        <item>Poor appetite or overeating</item>
        <item>Feeling bad about yourself - or that you are a failure or have let yourself or your
            family down
        </item>
        <item>Trouble concentrating on things, such as reading the newspaper or watching
            television
        </item>
        <item>Moving or speaking so slowly that other people could have noticed? Or the opposite -
            being so fidgety or restless that you have been moving around a lot more than usual
        </item>
    </array>
    <string name="intro_title_1">About this study</string>
    <string name="intro_desc_1">This study investigates the impact of using context-aware implementation intention (IF THEN plan) on mood reporting task.
            Research has shown that planning is more effective if you first identify a particular situation (IF),
            and decide on a goal for what you will do in that situation (THEN).</string>
    <string name="intro_title_2">Method</string>
    <string name="intro_desc_2">You will be given an IF THEN plan: \"IF it is in the evening, THEN I will complete the mood questionnaires.\"
            After a week, the app will ask you to specify the IF condition to be more specific that suits your availability.
            For example by specifying the time, location, and your activity.</string>
    <string name="intro_title_3">Reminder</string>
    <string name="intro_desc_3">After a week, the app will start sending you a daily reminder to complete the questionnaires when the specified condition is detected.</string>
    <string name="intro_title_4">Permission Request</string>
    <string name="intro_desc_4">We need you to grant a permission for location request in order to get an appropriate context of your specified condition.</string>
    <string name="service_not_available">Service not available</string>
    <string name="invalid_lat_long_used">Latitue and longitude are invalid</string>
    <string name="no_address_found">No address found</string>
    <string name="address_found">Address found</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

</resources>
